import 'package:quiz_app_tutorial/models/question.dart';

const List<Question> codingQuestions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. What is the output of the following code snippet in Python? \n\nprint(2 + 3 * 4)',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) 20',
      'b) 14',
      'c) 14',
      'd) 24',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. In JavaScript, what is the purpose of the "let" keyword?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Declare a constant variable',
      'b) Declare a block-scoped variable',
      'c) Declare a global variable',
      'd) Declare a function',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. Which data type is not supported in Python?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) int',
      'b) float',
      'c) str',
      'd) char',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. What does the acronym "HTML" stand for in the context of web development?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) HyperText Markup Language',
      'b) High Tech Multi-Language',
      'c) Home Tool Markup Language',
      'd) Hyperlink and Text Markup Language',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. Which programming language is often used for developing mobile applications in Android Studio?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Swift',
      'b) C++',
      'c) Java',
      'd) Python',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. What does the acronym "API" stand for in software development?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Advanced Programming Interface',
      'b) Application Programming Interface',
      'c) Automated Program Integration',
      'd) Algorithmic Programming Interface',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. In Python, how do you comment a single line of code?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) # This is a comment',
      'b) // This is a comment',
      'c) /* This is a comment */',
      'd) <!-- This is a comment -->',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. What is the purpose of the "git clone" command in Git?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Create a new branch',
      'b) Commit changes',
      'c) Copy a repository from a remote server',
      'd) Merge branches',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '9. What will be the output of the following code in Java?\n\nSystem.out.println("Hello, " + "World!");',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) HelloWorld!',
      'b) Hello, World!',
      'c) HelloWorld',
      'd) Hello,World!',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '10. In programming, what is a "for loop" used for?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Iterating over a sequence of elements',
      'b) Declaring variables',
      'c) Defining functions',
      'd) Handling exceptions',
    ],
  ),
];
